[
    {
        "question": "What is measured using a Richter scale?",
        "answer": "Earthquake"
    },
    {
        "question": "What product was originally manufactured by communications giant Nokia?",
        "answer": "Paper"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did Dark Side Of The Moon by Pink Floyd release?",
        "answer": "1973"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country would you find the Negev desert?",
        "answer": "Israel"
    },
    {
        "question": "When was the Pioneer 10 space probe launched into space?",
        "answer": "March 2, 1972"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the NATO phonetic alphabet word for X?",
        "answer": "Xray"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the SI physical unit of dynamic viscosity?",
        "answer": "Pascal-second"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year was the UK an Olympic Games host for the first time?",
        "answer": "1908"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many natural satellites does Jupiter have?",
        "answer": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Arizona?",
        "answer": "Phoenix"
    }
]